So a good set of instructions will always include an overview,
一个好的标注指南应该要包括任务概述 Overview、
the steps that contributors need to take to complete the job, rules, and tips.
任务步骤 Steps、规则和注意事项 Rules & Tips
In here, you should really include what contributors are looking for.
在“规则和注意事项”部分 你应该写明人工标注专家要在图像里标注的对象
So in this case, we're looking for parking signs in San Francisco,
在这个例子里 需要标注旧金山街景图里的停车标志
and then can include street cleaning,
种类包括：street cleaning、
accessible parking, no stopping, etc.
accessible parking、no stopping 等
You should provide rules for each of these.
同时 你需要制定识别规则
So if parking signs are partially observable,
比如 如果停车标志是部分可见
you should answer, yes.
那么应该选择 - 是
We do not want parking signs that are on garage doors, things like that.
如果停车标志在车库门口之类的 那么应该选择 - 否
You should also define what these parking signs look like.
你也需要定义这些停车标志的样貌
So in this case,
在这个情况下
text is generally not sufficient.
通常文字描述是不够的
So we have a table that includes a definition as well as an example of the sign.
因此 我们提供了一个表格 表格里有关于不同停车标志的定义描述以及图像示例
So here's our tow-away parking signs,
比如 这是一个拖车区停车标志
time limit parking signs, etc.
限时停车标志 等等
We also include further examples of images from the actual data set.
同时 我们也提供了真实数据集里的示例
We call out where the signs are to make it clear what we're looking for.
并在示例里标出了停车标志 再一次说明我们需要识别的对象
So in some of these, it's pretty hard to see.
有些图像里的停车标志很难发现
In this image in the top right,
在这张图像的右上角
we've got two parking signs in here.
这里有两个停车标志
So this case would be a yes.
所以答案是 - 是
We want to show where parking signs or obfuscated.
我们也展示了一些比较难发现的图像示例
So this one is behind a little tree but
比如 这个图像里 停车标志被一棵小树苗挡住了
we still want to make sure that contributors catch that,
我们希望引起人工标注专家的注意 让他们不要漏了这些情况
and we also want to include examples where there are no signs that we're looking for.
最后 我们希望展示一些没有停车标志的图像示例
So in this case, there are street signs but their speed limit, some warning sign.
比如 在这个图像里 街上有标志牌 但却是限速牌、警示牌
These don't include the parking signs we're looking for and
并不包括我们需要识别的停车标志
we want to make sure contributors are aware of that.
我们希望引起人工标注专家们的注意
Some of these don't contain any relevant signs.
也有一些示例完全不包含任何指示牌